PATRICK THOMAS WELLMAN

PatrickThomasWellman.com

GitHub.com/PatrickWellman

SUMMARY

Patrick specializes in building and deploying design focused mobile-responsive web applications. He has a well trained eye for aesthetically pleasing layouts and themes helping to improve overall user experience. Patrick possesses a strong knowledge of HTML5, advanced CSS3 and SASS. He is also familiar with working in React environments with the ability to create web applications with reusable components.

MAIN TECHNOLOGIES

React	JavaScript - ES6	React Router	CSS Grid	Semantic UI
HTML5	GitHub	CSS3 - Responsive UI	VS Code	Adobe

SASS SASSY CSS Color.Adobe

EXPERIENCE

Roventures, Web Developer, October 2019-Current

Patrick assisted in the development and proof of concepts for the rebuild of the video streaming platform. He focused on design, responsive layout, and implementing new libraries.

The Thompson Hotel, Pastry Chef, January 2018-Current

The Catbird Seat Restaurant, Executive Pastry Chef, June 2017-January 2018 **Meat Market Restaurants**, Corporate Pastry Chef, June 2016 - June 2017

Working as a Pastry Chef, Patrick has been in charge of remotely strategizing logistics, staffing, and delegating tasks for events in excess of 3000 people all while managing several departments of up to 40 people spread across a large territories. He has demonstrated excellent time management and communication skills, as well the ability to remain calm under pressure.

EDUCATION

Online Resources

Udemy: Modern React with Redux 2020, The Modern Javascript Bootcamp 2020, Advanced CSS and SASS, Build Responsive websites with HTML5 and CSS3, Code Academy, React & AWS Docs, YouTube, GitHub, StackOverFlow, Meetup, Hacker News, Code Newbie

REFERENCES

Rohan Damani, Lead Developer, Disney (864) 497-7223 Chef Zak Miller, Chef Instructor at The CIA - (917) 742-2122 Chef Kelly Fields, Corporate Pastry The Besh Group - (415) 699-4236